

- Bogotá
- tom.pujalte@gmail.com
- +57 322 7079680
- https://tompujalte.com/
- i⇔ French
- Open to remote work
- Driving license

Assets

- Ability to identify needs and determine best course of action based on specifications provided by client or project manager;
- Prioritisation of communication with back-end developers, managers and designers to ensure information exchange in the application;
- Use of best practices to structure HTML, CSS and Javascript;
- Use of frameworks like React to build powerful and modular applications;
- Rigorous operation of tests to verify application is running smoothly and correct code when necessary;
- Provision of website technical support and technical and functional website documentation for the customer.
- Ability to meet web development project deadlines, prioritise tasks based on their importance and manage time effectively

Languages

French

Native

English

Fluent

Spanish

Limited working proficiency

Interests

Street photography

Music

Drums and guitar

Social networks

(a) @pujaltetom

in @tom-pujalte

Tom Pujalte

Web developer

Passionate web developer with one year of experience, I am looking for challenging projects that will allow me to continue to develop and push the limits of my technical skills. I have a PVT visa that allows me to work in Colombia.

Available now

Work experience

App Developper

Since September 2023 Freelance Bogotá

- Coding applications and portfolio for individuals
- Creation of a social network with React for the Front, Node.js for the Back and MySQL for the data
- Learning of React Native for mobile applications

App Developer - JavaScript React

From April 2022 to June 2023 OpenClassrooms Paris

- Realisation of 14 projects/websites, including: sports statistics dashboard (with graphs), accommodation reservation site, integration of banking API
- Professional simulations of real world client requests

Trainee Journalist

From December 2019 to February 2020

Radio Caraïbes International Fort-de-France

- Drafting, recording and editing of radio reports, including use of Audacity
- Research and information gathering, including the realisation of more than 50 interviews

Trainee Journalist

From October 2018 to February 2019 La Dépêche du Midi Toulouse

- Drafting of web articles and print media for the Toulouse area
- Capture of illustration photos to accompany articles

Education

App Developpement - Javascript React (RNCP35976)

From April 2022 to June 2023 OpenClassrooms Paris

- Coding websites in Javascript, HTML, CSS
- Training in React, Sass, MongoDB
- Code management with Git and GitHub

Multimedia Journalism

From September 2017 to June Institut Supérieur de Journalisme de Toulouse (ISJT) 2020 Toulouse

- Training in web, print, radio and TV journalism
- Main subjects: English, Orthography, Geopolitics, Ethics and Media Law

Master in Cosmos, Fields and Particles (first year)

From September 2015 to June 2017 Faculté des Sciences Montpellier, Toulouse

• Main subjects: Astrophysics, Cosmology and Particle Physics

Bachelor of Science in Physics and Chemistry

From September 2011 to June 2014 Université de Nîmes Nîmes

 <u>Main subjects:</u> Fluid Mechanics, Organic Chemistry, Applied Mathematics, Quantum Physics

Computer skills

Programming languages

- JavaScript
- HTML/CSS

Frameworks/Librairies

- React, React Native, MySQL
- Chart.js, Redux, Sass